<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marc Tudurí</title>
    <link>https://marctuduri.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Marc Tudurí</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 22:52:28 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://marctuduri.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Prometheus for monitoring Django applications in Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://marctuduri.com/blog/using-prometheus-for-monitoring-django-applications-in-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 23:09:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marctuduri.com/blog/using-prometheus-for-monitoring-django-applications-in-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Django application deployment architecture Developing web applications with Django is very easy and fun: if you just follow the tutorial in a few hours you can have up and running your own website. However, deploying a Django site can be hard and you can end up running a site with a terrible performance if you don&amp;rsquo;t follow the recommended guidelines to deploy a Django site to a production environment.
There are many options to deploy a Django application but you will finish using a WSGI (Web Server Gateway Interface) which is a Python specification that describes how a webserver communicates with web applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://marctuduri.com/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 22:52:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marctuduri.com/books/</guid>
      <description>Technical books that I&amp;rsquo;m currently reading, I already read or they are pending to read.
Reading  Fundamentals of Software Architecture: An Engineering Approach Functional Programming in Scala Designing Data-Intensive Applications Quantum Computing for Computer Scientists  Read  Prometheus: Up &amp;amp; Running Introducing Istio Service Mesh for Microservices Kubernetes Cookbook Kubernetes Up &amp;amp; Running Designing Distributed Systems The Hacker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Scaling Python Fundamentals of Deep Learning Clean Code Introduction to Algorithms Two Scoops of Django Test-Driven Development with Python Writing Idiomatic Python The C Programming Language Operating Systems  To Read  Clean Architecture Distributed Systems SQL Performance Explained Hackers &amp;amp; Painters The Pragmatic Programmer Hackers: Heroes of the Computer Revolution  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New site with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://marctuduri.com/blog/new-site-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marctuduri.com/blog/new-site-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
My old site was a little bit abandoned and hard to update so I decided to renew it.
For this time, I decided to use a static site generator so I gave a chance to Hugo. I never tried before but I discovered that it has its own themes site which is awesome as saves you a lot of customization time. By the way, if you wonder what template I&amp;rsquo;m using is the Cocoa enhanced theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://marctuduri.com/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marctuduri.com/home/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Marc!
I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer focused in backend and infrastructure systems. I like distributed systems and software architecture. I speak mostly Python, Go and Scala. Currently, I work as a Software Engineer in SoundCloud.
Proud FSF member for almost a decade, Open Source maintainer and technical conferences attender.
Besides that, I&amp;rsquo;m a music nerd, audiophile and instrumental rock guitar player (Fura). I also love beer and homebrewing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source</title>
      <link>https://marctuduri.com/open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marctuduri.com/open-source/</guid>
      <description>I love free software so I spent some of time contributing to many open source projects either fixing bugs, improving documentation or adding new features. Here is a list of some projects that I maintain or contribute.
Backend Maintainer   periskop: Exception aggregator for micro-service environments.
  Puput: A Django blog app implemented in Wagtail.
 wordpress-to-puput: Import your Wordpress blog data into Puput. blogger-to-puput: Import your Blogger blog data into Puput.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>